(Amy:)A colleague of mine did her
graduate thesis on the fungus
(Amy:)that grows on improperly
sterilized manicure implements.
(Amy:)Well don't tell me
that's not "girl talk."
(Penny:)So where should
we go tonight?
(Penny:)A bar? A club? A movie?
(Bernadette:)Or we could just stay here.
(Amy:)Yes, and continue to bond.
(Amy:)I have a feeling
that after tonight,
(Amy:)one of you will become
my best friend forever.
Or "BFF," if you prefer.
(Amy:)Which I don't.
(Penny:)All right, time to open
Bachelor Number Two.
(Bernadette:)Gee, I don't know
if I should drink more.
(Bernadette:)I have to drive home,
and I've got enough trouble
(Bernadette:)seeing over the dashboard
as it is.
(Penny:)That's okay.
You can just sleep here.
(Amy:)Oh, good, a slumber party!
(Amy:)We'll do makeovers,
initiate phony phone calls,
(Amy:)and have spirited pillow fights
in our frilly nighties!
(Penny:)Oh, gosh, Amy.
(Penny:)I don't know if I would call
this an actual slumber party.
(Amy:)Well, that's disappointing.
(Amy:)I've always wanted to be
invited to a slumber party.
(Bernadette:)Oh, you never were?
(Penny:)Not even when
you were a kid?